teenfreeway.com 2008-05-14

# TeenFreeway - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Our goal in collecting personal information from you upon registration is to provide you, the user, with the best experience possible by targeting site content and advertisements to our audience.   Your information is stored in our database and not released to any outside parties.   We will not sell, rent, or distribute any of the registration information that you provide to us without your consent. 

But please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily give out any personally identifying information to any merchant listed on our site, that this information can be collected and used by others.   You should always check the privacy policies of each merchant featured on TeenFreeway.com.   Personally identifying information includes your name, your home or other physical address, e-mail address, telephone number or any information that makes you identifiable.   If you post any of this personally identifying information in online areas that are accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

TeenFreeway is by definition for teenagers (i.e. 13 and older) -- and older folks who are teenagers at heart!  You must be 13 or older to participate in any TeenFreeway promotions.  For those sites for which TeenFreeway is a conduit, again, you must read the privacy guidelines of that site which may differ materially from those of TeenFreeway. 

The United States Children's Online Privacy Protection Act went into effect on April 21st, 2000. In order to comply with that law, TeenFreeway will not knowingly process any data that was submitted to us by a visitor who is under 13 years of age.  TeenFreeway is all about providing the best freebies on the web for teenagers.

Please [Visit http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy) for information from the Federal Trade Commission about protecting children's online privacy.

****
